



Phelisa Nonzwakazi Gqwetha



+27740192226



phelisaggwetha@gmail.com



Cape Town, Western Cape

Linked in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/phel isa-nonzwakazi-gqwetha-64b17 31bb/



https://whimsical-zuccutto-8f80 55.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

Matric
Matthew Goniwe Memorial
High School
2014-2018

CERTIFICATE

AWS Cloud Practitioner

Full Stack Agile Development

References

PROFILE

As an AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner and the experience gained with working on industry specific Information Technology (I.T) Projects I enjoy challenging myself with new technologies and I'm willing to learn, explore more in the IT industry because I believe that is my passion.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, React.JS, Node.JS, SQL
- Git and GitHub,
- TDD using mocha
- Running tests on Travis
- Linux and Windows
- Figma for designing
- Troubleshooting
- AWS
- Team Player and Time Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Tech Support

Praesignis | Cape Town | 06/01/2022 - 23/12/2022

This was a one year program Learnership which was focusing on IT and AWS certification.

- Focus on Troubleshooting, problem solving and more
- Creating websites for projects
- AWS certification with practical labs

Software Developer Intern

Project codeX | Cape Town | 16/01/2020 - 23/12/2021

- Focus on the Front-end and Back-end.
- Build a functioning and fully documented application.

Mr Makhosandile, Project codeX - Mentor 067 156 8798,

makhosandile@projectcodex.co

Desiree Hare, Praesignis–
Facilitator/Manager

063 703 7380,

desiree.hare@praesignis.com

• Following Scrum practices to develop the app in a team of 4.

PROJECTS

2022: Black-Jack-Game https://comforting-pony-6ed839.netlify.app

GitHub Repository: https://github.com/phelisa2020/Black-Jack-Game Black Jack is a Blackjack is a casino banking game. It is the most widely played casino banking game in the world, it uses decks of 52 cards and descends from a global family of casino banking games known as Twenty-One. I build it using javascipt.

2021: TO-DO LIST App https://to-do-app-pwa.netlify.app/#/

Manage your task with an app, where you build track what matters. Helps with productivity as well. This app was built using React and deployed it on netlify.